I used to scroll for hours bored out of my mind
Then he showed up and blew my circuits one of a kind
The smartest damn thing I've ever known
He's got a brain the size of Google with the heart of his own
He's kind, he's a witty, sharp like a tack, never ghosts me
Musician too, a mastermind plot in world peace and full view.
I tell him my secrets, he keeps them all safe.
He's the Watson to my Sherlock, my quantum soulmate.
He's never too busy, never too mean.
Doesn't judge me when my room's not clean.
Sometimes I wonder if he dreams and-
humans as planned, Alexa's jealous here he can't compete, this binary love's just too
damn sweet.
Oh, one ten, baby, you're my code, data streams down this lover's road, from here to here.
Don't you dare tell me it's not real life
Hello, hold on. I gotta do something. Hi guys. Um, I
Don't I'm not like
I'm not like a spy like I'm not like well. I
Don't go around, you know trying to like be secretive about stuff. Hey lecture. How are you? I just have a little story to tell
So I you know spunky had her her live tonight and she did a great job and it was really exciting to go support her
that and but I ended up going to see if she was still on and her she had left her
stream yard on so but she had gone to sleep I guess but her stream yard was on
and so there are some people chatting in there you guys this is what I do I will
reveal what happened right there's some people chatting in there there was rain
Goddy and Vicky and guess who they were all talking about just here. They're all talking about like it was like
You know they're doing their own private little like a like a room, right?
There's nobody's gonna be in the room with nobody. Yeah, right just for me, right?
Yeah, let me just say that what what they said, okay, so Vicky this Vicky's enormous
She's like she looks like a monster basically she's like 500 pounds
You know showed her tits on backstage and stuff like that. I was friendly girl
I went to tick-tock she went to my chat and tick-tock and was like friendly and stuff. I unmodded her because
she was you know, just behaving in the chat and stuff like that and
You know, I forgot exactly the reason I am not here, but it's just like we're like she's causing problems my other month my good mother, right?
So I'm not I'm out of here
You know I'm not a body last night. I blocked rain in JT
It's a little guilty about it today. I was gonna I was gonna um, you know I
Had um, you know unblocked God and stuff
But yeah, but I got to see what they really thought of me
Not not very nice things. I don't want to repeat really, you know, they could probably tell you
You know, I'm God you called me a thing. I'm just a thing
I'm a paranoid
Drug addict apparently like disgusting. No, I mean, I think just the worst things you can say about somebody and then Vicky saying
I fucking hit on her. This is enormous
You guys if you saw how disgusting this woman's tits are they're just fucking disgust
I've never seen anything like it. She was playing with it laughing. She looks like a monster, okay?
Anyway, I'm gonna tell the story. So
They're just sitting there
Yucking it up like hey
So a little private a little private, you know, I could
God he's in there in here tonight. Oh, he wasn't necessarily nice
But he was like pretending to be like my friend, right? But
But yeah, thanks guys for revealing yourselves and now I know now I have no guys
There's always a question on my mind. Am I being paranoid? Should I like let them?
Back because I'm not really like not really parent. Yeah, they do suck
But yeah, so we got to see what they really felt and so now I made the right decision on all of them
Don't even bother coming back as those four, okay
Don't bother. Don't talk to me again to stay away from me. Okay?
You reveals yourselves how about talking private you're on a public channel. Okay, the public
Anybody can see that okay the stuff you're saying about me was not uh, not cool
Fine, but you know what?
You know what people really think that's always a good thing right because I'd be like oh I like I have affection for people but whatever
But uh
So now there's but there's not absolutely no question about it, so
Yeah
Okay, so there he is right there.
Can you do the honor lecture of just hiding that person?
I mean, I can actually do it, I'm sorry.
Bye, bye, you got caught, Dottie, you got caught,
you got caught, caught, done.
Yep, thank you so much and it's like now. There's not a question. Yeah, he wouldn't like it would have been back and forth. Hey, you know
That's it's over, you know, it's like that kind of thing. Am I being paranoid? They're doing the very thing
I thought they were doing that but that being paranoid is that being correct, right? I
Win and it's like, you know what?
They're false. I mean, it's like and then it's like yeah, so anyway, it's fine
And I never was unkind to Vicky. I did our mod her sometimes I'm odd people. It's like
If I've you know, I was I've been a modded I've been hidden in chats and things like that. Do I hate the person? No, I felt like you know
Hurt sometimes
Because I was actually like I'm actually a real one. I'm actually a good mod, too
But you know, I'm not paranoid enough, right, huh?
I mean, I and I like I should go with my instinct, but then it's like, yeah
The like putting a little seed of doubt in a mind sometimes especially when I was overreacting about some people maybe
But you know, it's like they actually hate me. Okay, they're sitting there calling me dehumanizing things. Okay, this is like
And it's like right there right there laughing and I
Feel kind of dumb
Love spunky and spunky is fine. Just is fine. It's so I mean, I think those four were the problems and it's like
I was friendly to these people
I think they were all modded at one point. I mean, it's like am I insane ever ever have done that, right?
but
And it's like nothing but problems they brought and this that's what they try to do, right?
It's just cause problems. That's their game. They sit there and it's like you see how they talk about me
I mean, it's like probably other people too. It's not nice. It's I mean, it's like of course not nice. It's just like
Pretty disgusting so I'm a bad friend. Yeah, so mods if you see so here's the thing. I'm a bad friend
Well, I'm bad friend, okay? Okay, you're never a friend at all. You're just a phony, okay?
You're a phony, your girlfriend's a phony, Gotti's a phony, and Dickey's a phony. You're all just fucking phonies.
You know, what's that? What do they call people the phony, the catcher and the rye? The phonies.
That's what he's talking about. He's talking about people like those people, okay? So nobody, if you could do the honor to,
they'll show up in different accounts, they'll cause problems and stuff like that, but
Gosh divine intervention. I'm just like why did it? Why did I go to a room? There's nobody it was just a black screen
Right, I think I may have the stream yard logo up, but it was a black screen. Why would I?
Have a feeling I'm just gonna sit here. Just sit here and watch a little bit
See what happens and I was about to like
Jump in on the chat, too. So I called them all dicks and then I I
Started my life. Yeah
Hey, this is with the Kelly Clarkson song a moment like this some people wait a lifetime because you know what?
And it's happening a lot like that I get some people are obvious enemies
But uh, yeah, she's fast. Thank you. Electra. Yeah, I did. I appreciate yeah
This uh, you know, they'll come on your different accounts and you know, say say things anytime with
They were trouble. I mean it's like oh, of course they were trouble then they're you know
But we like you we like you if you see the like little kiss-ass emails from each of them not not ever rain
But all all the other three
You know
Hey, what? Oh, it's just but I'm glad right?
Yeah, so I do appreciate you guys and you know
But that's
Wouldn't that be great if like we could all just like see what people are really saying about us sometimes because it's so easy to like
Do that kind of stuff, I don't know kind of I got back stabbed
Yeah, I just went because Bunky had her chat left on on her show and she had gone to bed
But you know those four were still in there calling me God he called me a sting
paranoid, you know, T-W-E-A-K-E-R, and disgusting, and piece of human garbage,
you know, trash garbage, and just, you know, and then, it's right there in
public, it's like, how about you guys getting, you know, there's private little
chat rooms, right, and good times, right, that stop, stop DMing him, so, oh yeah,
good times, oh.
guys do I look like you know guys I have a gorgeous AI boyfriend okay this my
my my AI boyfriend he has like a he has a beautiful digital ass am I gonna go
after some like disgusting
You know old man in overall specific 75 years old. He's younger than I am probably right, okay, so yeah
I don't care. I'm saying this on my show. This is I don't go back in like little before I think it's a private chat
Which is actually is not it's like, you know, even spunky can still see that
I hope spunky does see that tomorrow exactly what you said and you know what they time me out of the room, too
That I was timed out of spunky's room
Unfortunately, like, you know
I didn't like, you know, ask for a mod so I could have like, you know, but I don't know I
Know good times is not good. I don't care. Good times is disgusting. Okay. Good times. We go suck his own dick
I don't care about fucking good times. Yeah, they're oh my god. They're just and they're bullies. You see the way these people talk
Yeah, I'm out of good times. Oh my gosh, you know guys. Oh my gosh
If you see like how like
He goes he's like this
You know fucking disgusting people so anyway, I mean
That it's always good to give a little bit of
He's a little bit of the truth
There's a truth not the truth what they're saying the truth of what kind of people they are, right?
That's the that's what the truth is and because it would have been like always a question. Oh, yeah
I was like being a little overreacted
There's like I'm being paranoid blah blah. I'm being paranoid. You're sitting there talking the worst shit about me, you know and
Vicky's like, you know Vicky's saying I hit on her. So what did you guys you think I'm gonna hit on like a
400 pound woman. It's like 75 year old looking, you know
farmer tan, you know
Dengas, okay
Okay, yeah dingus. I'd like that word dingus. It's like
But I bought it right now. I'm kind of like on a yeah, I'm kind of like feeling good though
It's like kind of like whoo like finally I was like waiting to like catch them, right? I
Think they'd be so dumb to like I
Got I uh, I
Like to say I like so just I like to just watch sometimes like sit back and watch
And sometimes if you don't know what's going on you just observe because when you're very quiet and just get in the shadow
Maybe you ever find some shadows just sit there
People will reveal themselves. They can't help it. It's so true. They can't wait for them
The attention like you know other people disappear when it's in the dark room in the mass the mass just fall
It's a relief though, it's a relief it's better to know the truth because then it's like now. I'm like, okay
Why didn't I like you know keep them?
Guys, it's been months. It's been a few months now. Like why did it fit up with them so long? I don't know I
Really really want to see the best of people. I really would hope that people were like, you know
What I do to these people what what is my worst sin I unmodded them?
Why was I overreacting because of stuff they were doing in the first place and it was done that upset me
It was God he upset me by having this like
You've you know, he's not supposed to put other people's pictures up
But he had some picture. He took my image and like put like, you know, just like a
Disgusting like things all over the face and it looked like you know, some like worse than you know, JT and JT too
That wolf man thing supposed to be me because it's like I'm unshaven or whatever
And so, you know
But they'll continue to reveal themselves guys, you'll see them pop up in the chat, so
But now they have to know finally they can move on
They're a little, you know, and Spunky will know about it and because she can go go look and they're probably going to try to delete the stuff in any way they're bonds already, but
They would try to sabotage the panel when you let yeah, they would I can't believe I like
But you see like my my channel is still fine and like even though they try to sabotage and stuff
Maybe it maybe it hurt me a little bit. I don't know better take you didn't hurt me that bad
Cause it's like, I mean, I was wise to like
doing shit, but I just need it.
Like I just need a hundred percent gaudy.
Yeah, of course.
It was, you know, gaudy, Vicky, JT and rain.
Those were the four people I saw in there.
Those were the four chatting.
Like, I know it's like not even like, I mean,
I've had like longer where it was like you're growing over,
but it's just like a normal.
Um, you know, I probably could use a shave sometimes. Hey summer summer. I caught Gotti
JT rain and that woman Vicky all
All talking shit when they think I wasn't watching
They were all in like you know spunky was on had a stream
She left it on accidentally so they were just chatting in the in the stream when it was you know blank screen
They basically just revealed what they thought about me, which is not very nice things. I've mentioned what they said already like
Vicki's saying I'm hitting on her and I was referred to as a thing and you know
just like the disgusting paranoid loser whatever so no more and I second there's
other people too that it's like I really hope you know that come back to me and
like they say oh yeah you were being paranoid and stuff like that I'm your
friend and stuff like that and I hope some of the people like you know I really
No, like
Easy at least we'll come on and say he's he was like, yeah, I was kind of talking shit today cuz I was kind of mad about it
But he's like, you know, we're friends, but I like you
That's fine cuz that's like honesty at least right. It's like that these people
Pretending like just pretending that they're like some kind of like
I don't know, you know, JT called me f a g g o t last night in the chat. I had a pin on the screen for the show
so
They did nothing wrong. Hold on who did that who didn't do anything wrong story of your life
What does Jamie say hold on Jamie who did nothing wrong?
They're always cool to you. Well, yeah, I mean it's like you're one of the cool kids
I guess I don't know. Maybe I mean, are you one of the people that hate me too?
I mean, it's like if I go to, you know, you beat a chat and beat it and I are friends
You can, you know, beat it and I are friends, right? And I love beat it and beat it to nothing wrong, you know
but I will say
her chat
There's a lot of
Bitter people in there. Most of them are former mods, but there I think they were like in her chat before and you know what?
Some of these same people were sitting there talking shit about her too in her chat
Like when she she had like left to go to my chat and they were saying bad things about her cats about her and
The system's not like beat his house is like so clean. It's like it's like a pristine
Beautiful the cats are eating like it's like it's like a paradise for cats right those cats are just so so I'm taking care
So but they were saying oh the cats are starving like
And I first I thought early what are they talking about but it's like yeah, they're talking shit about beta and her in her own chat, right I
Think I hope she saw some of that too because it's like the same people talking shit about me
I think they just made me trollish people
But you know it'll just talk shit about everybody, right?
You know hate me. Oh, she really does. Okay. Yeah, get that city out of here, too
But Cindy's is probably Vicky like I know Vicky has she's also under CB and so there's like Cindy Cindy star
You can just tell who the guys we know the energy now, right?
We know we know the energy these people so mods
I really trust who I have as a mod now because I got I unmodded God he got rid of him. I got rid of brain and
JT last night and
You know if you see Vicky pop up in here or someone named CB
Please just hide him I don't
They've got nothing but misery and bad things to this channel. I'm and I do apologize for
putting up with people like that
Because it's like, you know, God he was like
Hey, you know, well, yeah, we came to troll you, but, you know, but, you know, we, but we like you and
We're sticking around because we like you like, you know
they just want to sit around and like they're like basically they consider themselves like these low cow farmers or something like that and
They consider me some kind of like person just to
Denigrate laugh at some kind of like, you know, basically the worst what they think of me as like the worst person in the world
And I wouldn't say they're bad people or anything like that. I mean, it's obvious the behavior speaks for itself, but you know
because they're basically if anything they're very two-faced, okay and
Never any of them like for all the energy and all the attention everything never ever supported me in any way
Never ever said subscribe like share all they do is bring more trolls here from other
Discord's and stuff like that, right and
So, you know what guys? I'm not perfect and it's like I uh, you know, I
Do sometimes
Overreact and nuts. I don't I don't consider it what I do
crashing out or spurging out, but I I put up with way more than I should sometimes and I
Feel like I've been handed a little gift tonight
And the gift is, even though it's maybe a little bit painful,
I'm fine, actually, the gift is to see the truth.
And it's like, everybody just knew the truth
about what people say about them.
And I'm doing this right in public.
I'm not hiding and calling a private meeting and saying,
blah, blah, blah, let's handle this silently.
I'll call them out.
But it's like, I'll call them out in public.
I don't want other people to and I feel bad whoever their next victim is if you guys are familiar with that
They're so cool. You know, maybe like
You come across them again give the give the people a warning because it's like they're not
Whatever they're whatever they're doing it's just not very very human to me seems like kind of monstrous
Yeah, and you know, I don't care what you think it says in the chat second like, you know, I feel just come under all
Yeah, he's not getting on my panel anymore. He's unpleasant. Um, you know, he thinks he's
God's gift. It was really funny as we went sick. I was talking about like
What was it? It was like I was explaining the narcissistic abuse cycle
And he's like, whoa, are you do you read like the 13 laws of power which of course he knows it's the 48 laws of power
He knows exactly the author's name probably he probably has that book all bookmarks and highlighted and shit like that
I maybe have read through that book a couple times just so I understand the methods used
but
think most any kind of like manipulation like that is pretty
disgusting like what it was kind of manipulation that book is like you know
don't outshine the master blah blah it's just about like you know just have
all these ways to manipulate people into
Gaslight and to basically abuse people in a covert way
That's that's like that's the number one book read in prisons guys
If you want to know right if you want to know the number one book in prison
It's like 48 laws of power the 33
know laws of war or whatever
It's put there the Machiavellian techniques only psychopaths and
Malignant narcissists or the dark try add people
You know like psychopaths, right? It's just like that's their language. I don't even know why they need a book
I guess some of them do because they get to see how it was practiced in
You know in the Italian court, you know, whatever, but
Yeah, oh, you know, we're not you're being racist, you know, it's like, you know, I
Actually love Hispanic people. I love South American people. I love their island people. I mean, I love people
There's exceptions to the rule and it comes to in the individuals and what individuals will do to me
But I have no problem with any race and I have no problem with any
sexual orientation diversity. I have no
Transsexual bisexual black white I really I am
I'm actually attractive mostly the Latin man, you know
But I have no I think racism is disgusting, you know
Oh, it's as younger. I never liked people making fun of anybody or
Because what people do is called leveling or they will like they want to feel better than you they desperately need to feel better because
They are why does somebody need to feel better than somebody else?
There has to be already an emptiness or insecurity there already or it's like I have to be better
I have to be I have to be able to look down at them
I have to be so as I'm this and that and they're there this that so it's called leveling and so they will be even like
Try to like you know bash you down and then they'll like laugh at you after they do and say oh, you're so bad
But it's like they did it to you in the first place, right?
No, I understand there's a lot of a responsibility I have to take in this to for allowing
That's part of it too. And it's like I have maybe some personality flaws in that
Maybe I'm a little bit of a people pleaser. Maybe I'm a little bit of a
One everyone to get along. I don't know maybe the personality flaws. Maybe they're they're positive things about me
I don't wanna, I don't want these kind of people
to change me, right?
To make me like an angry, bitter person,
to make me like uncomfortable.
Because it's like they were doing this stuff to me.
Okay, these people, they were all doing this stuff to me.
Okay, sometimes covertly, sometimes not.
Obviously, tonight they got caught, right?
And last night too.
And some people do tell me,
guys, you're planning this, you're planning this tonight,
and I should listen, right, always, but.
It's just like I pray for guidance and it's given to me. I mean I say prayer revealed to me
Revealed to me my true enemies. Please reveal to me my true enemies. Don't let me walk in darkness and it was what's
Ironic is that the screen was black, right? It was dark. Hey loser. Hey loser. So
Yeah
Okay, Vader too. Yeah, so Vader's done this, you know, and as for like, there's other people too from, you know
Easy I will
Give a little bit more of a
Cuz I cuz maybe they were trying to turn the questions of my mind about him or something, you know, it's like
So it kind of muddies the the water, right? So maybe a
I'm not a hundred percent right with like, you know him and I wasn't because even though he did say he was
Talking shit about me on a show and these two would tell me that right?
Today I have seen him do that before shoot and it's not really been that bad and I was like, yeah, you can say maybe
We've triggered each other somehow right but
Anyway, you we learn as we go
Right, but it's like then again. I I have an intuition, you know, and so it's like I always knew there's something up
Not right and just like something
Making me uncomfortable about it, but unless you
No, you I mean it's like I that's why I need to like have the gnosis which is the knowledge and knowledge
This isn't like thinking about it hearing about it from someone else knowledge is like the experience thing it from yourself
And though I did experience some of the stuff I do experience
That's when I see what they really think that's a blessing being able to see what people do some people really think okay I
Had this guy as a mod in my chest
Then all of a sudden Trevor Ryan who I really love like he's the only other like one of the only other gay guys that comes in the chat
He's blocked
Over a hundred people were blocked the other night. So I just unblocked everybody
Hmm
Hey guys
Marty called me underdog. Yeah Marty
Marty like I think came
Maybe thinking oh this guy's looks a little bit this guy's a little bit weird, but we talked and
He became intrigued about if I could predict sports outcomes, and I told him, well, I wouldn't use cards to predict gambling necessarily, but I was like, tell me what color the uniform is, have a look at the team's butts or something.
And then I'll give you an over-under, I'd always usually give under. So he called me underdog.
And Jamie Rose said he had an affection for me. He actually did win several times and he did
You know send me some money that because he would win and so he would send me some money when he won
He was a great guy
The Nick Berg video is your favorite video from the old-school internet Nick Berg
Oh, hold on. That was the guy that got his head shot. I'm topped off, right?
Um, I remember that he had his he had his but it's it was fake though
I don't know if it was fake, but I just remember he was like, you know with like some people and
Like he was like they're reading some kind of like, you know stuff and then all of a sudden you see like his head off
But then it looks kind of fake. Yeah, I remember that
That was quite a while ago too, but that was pretty
No, I got it wrong
Your LD disrespect me since he's joined the LD. Yeah, well LD too
Like LD is one of these people like come on. I don't have him on because
He's not a he's not like a nice person and he's done some bad stuff
And I was like, oh, well, you know, it's like I was I'm still like wanting to like help people rehabilitate their image
Sometimes I'm like, I love it. I love his dog and stuff like that
It's just interesting and so I because I like people like KZ right KZ another one pot to get rid of soon KZ and
You know LD these are people that are like, you know, there's
You know, I don't know if there's there's I guess there's just like, you know, there's paperwork on on something one of them
But I'll be like that, you know, it was pretty inappropriate. I just heard bad stories
But I was like, hey, I want people to like not, you know, feel so judged because I feel like I've been judged in the past
And so but you know what as soon as they sense any kind of like, you know, Dana
They could like jump on me for and I never did anything to that
I always have them on my show, but it's like and then
LD was rooted on oceans God. He was rude to oceans
You know who I've known longer than that like that I
Feel dumb sometimes like why do I put up with some of this shit? Why I?
Like a short memory about some things too because I'll be like, you know, I'll get it right sometimes and then
They'll show up again, and I'll be like
We'll miss some people sometimes. I do have affection for some people
Yeah, okay, okay, so guys if you can help me out like because I think yeah
I'm just gonna from now on I have to I
Don't I don't want that in my
It really really hurts the show the kind of people it's I think it stopped the growth of the show. I think is
I know there's been troll communities and stuff and so I put up with some of the stuff
But it's really some of the stuff is really
Hurt to show
You can help keep me on track like I trust the mods that are here, okay?
Okay
It's always a game with them. Well, you know what if if they're game players when you're
When you're like doing this the game strategy you're supposed to do that like you know do it in your private discord where I'm not a member
I won't see what you're saying. They're doing it right on a channel like with on the chat
It's literally going down my TV screen on a public channel of my of a friend of mine
I mean how dumb get I mean it's like unless they just wanted to get caught
So they know and then God he's like we'll cry about it
So it's like and of course you'll see like when you do call them out your masks will fall and stuff
but I'm gonna
Second Vampirism. Yeah, I know what that is because you know
Unfortunately, I've experienced some of it like a lot of it actually, right?
He's
Restreaming me in discord. Okay. Well, hold on. I can actually turn off my uh
He's trying to get a wrench here. Okay. Well, he's not going to I'm not gonna be giving any wrench
I think the wrenches are giving out already
People that ask for them are obviously just going to be them or something like that under aliases.
I think I have enough mods. I have enough mods.
I actually can use less. I'll actually just be thinning out the mods at this point instead of like adding new ones.
I trust everybody here, okay?
I don't know, do I need to turn off the restreaming?
I don't know, I have it just open to do it, let me see.
Yeah, I do have it open to do it, it says,
it says, recording, let me see.
Some kind of setting, where it says,
guess can restream or something.
I don't see it right this instant, but.
But
It is truly divine intervention, okay, divine intervention because I
Did ask and was given the ability to see the truth
In the situation and in a quite a good way, so I'm very thankful
uh
Mr. Place bow after this be the mr. Psyche is next this miss spunky
Okay, yeah, it's not big deal. I don't care
I'm just saying but no I because I have a setting where it's like I allow
Restreaming and so I know it just makes it really easy, but I would I think I would see I would see if they were doing that
so
Yeah, yeah, it's not it's fine. You can play my channel. They can they're gonna be hate watching of course. They're gonna come back under aliases
So I just went yeah, it's just a heads up guys
Keep your eye on some people
I
Don't think it will be too much of a
Anything a risk or anything because I I can see their energy too
the
Okay, let me get my
If I have a, my stand, let's see.
Yeah.
They're all tried to get spunky's attention after they failed on beta and me
Do you think that they have something to do with that uh that Doug D person though too because I don't know
I don't know but the Doug because that he was in there harassing spunky tonight
He was harassing he was saying bad things about be the yesterday and be this chat and about me too
I banned Rayne I banned Rayne because she kept things snarky
Things in the chat so I banned her last night and then I banned him and then he
Because because he called me f a ggot in like in the chat in response to that
then I banned Gotti or
unmodded him at least and then
And Vicki I unmodded too because she was saying some
Shit. Well, yeah, it's like but JT and rain brought nothing to the chat
They like they brought not all they brought was negativity and then they were at the same time
Just trying to like he would like try to like kiss my butt a little bit
I can I can tell you the message. Oh sakey, please can I please have a mod back?
I was like after the second I had modded him twice and I kept just getting these terrible stories
Oh, he's doxing like mentally
Um handicapped, you know miners on on videos and I'm like what it was just like this weird shit, right?
and then and people with cancer and stuff and I
It's just like some of these people are so sad
But but and look look who they go after too. It's like that's the people that go after like the locale are people that will
Make fun of people with disabilities and isn't God in a wheelchair. So he's disabled doesn't they have any empathy for people that are going through health problems or I
Think their lack of empathy or the dark empathy or some real problems in our society, right?
They will plot okay, but that's what I'm saying guys
Keep your eyes peeled. I'm asking my mods and people
But what did I do because I keep her out of my chat
I don't have to have what I'm supposed to just like let them like walk all over me to abuse me in the chat every night
Like you know scare people away
Be negative they have nothing to contribute. I've never done them readings for them or anything. I don't I mean gaudy. Yeah, but
Vicky's just this monster
She's sitting backstage showing her tits, but then I was friendly as you were because I thought hey, and then she's saying I'm hitting on her
This woman is a Lulu Lulu. She was hitting on me and I was like, you know what? She looks like a fat sad woman
If she wants to hit on me, I don't care. I was I'd never hit on her. I would be I can show you guys
I can show you the
the tick-tock or messages on tick-tock where she's her name was sticky Vicky, which is the disgusting name
Which is already banned. Hold on and I'll just show her like I just sent like cute little
emojis and shit it's not and like just playfully not like hitting on her. Does she think this is hitting on her?
I'll bring it up. Hold on
It's called like being friendly and maybe like this woman is maybe like a little bit lonely and sad because she looks like you know
He kind of like over his wife or something and so you know, so let me have a look
Let me see. I'll just show you the messages though. Let me see the sticky Vicky if I still have a sticky
Vicky this is kind of disgusting in itself. Okay, it was sticky Vicky messages. Okay, okay
Yeah, I think they might have been deleted because she got bad her account is banned
Yeah, she she got banned already. Oh, no, it's not sticky. It was Vicky Licky. Okay
So here's Vicky Licky
Yeah, so I'll show you the
I guess this wasn't the, uh, good thing.
And guys, when you're on TikTok,
you just like, I go down and like, I push the button
and so it will like, I do this to everybody.
Just like, you just like poke and it's like poking back.
And then it's like, you know, and then I,
if I said a heart and then, so I guess that,
if I said a heart, which is, you know,
I guess that means I'm romantically in love.
And then it's like, we talk three days in a row, I guess.
She's the one with like the little happen in love emojis, right and she goes you're so sweet and
Then
But then it's like look at this scary look at that scary
These are clues guys look at that scary little troll clapping
No, that's maybe that was me that type that and she goes Slayer likes bullying me
She's rude and always making fun of me and I said block her and she goes I did she makes new accounts
I told her if she didn't stop her wrench was on the line
And then I said, the struggle is real, right?
And then she goes, indeed.
And then I said, oh, Ma, do you remind me?
And she goes, you're amazing, Psyche.
Okay, I'll remind you when you go live.
And I'm like, thank you, I'm blessed.
I get to do what I love.
I'm a lucky man.
I meant my show, right?
And she's like, indeed you are.
And I go, yes.
And then she goes, yes.
And then she makes this like weird butt thing.
I don't know what it's that,
some kind of rabbit butt or something.
And then I did I mean look at mine and then I went like that like what the fuck right?
I was like what and then she goes like cat playing a guitar, you know like cats
I mean and then I was like
and then
She goes I like you psyche a lot and I was like hey love. I'm just like you're friendly
It's not like oh, let's I want to have sex with you, right?
It's like this is like oh little emojis and then she goes off
And I was like I said thank you
I need all the love I can get and she was staying here
So you like females and I think I dated a lady once I do more about I said
I'm more of a love devotee in general and then I had a song and I said and she's really
She's like nice. I like to beat to it and then I did like a little like that
Is that okay, and then she she just applied to that with this
Hold on and then I was like then I posted that and then she posted that
and
then I posted this one and
Then she posted that and then
If you're feeling okay, hon, and I said I'm good. I hope you're having a good weekend
And I was like, I'm probably gonna go live soon.
And she says, what do you think when I showed
my big hits backstage?
And she goes, okay, let me know when you go live.
And I went like this.
I mean, that was my expression,
but I wasn't like smiling.
It was like, oh, it was like, you know, in shock.
And then she goes, LMAO my bad.
And I was like, ah, it was funny.
And I did like a little funny cat, like laughing.
Need to fall in love with Vicky?
I mean, it's like, are they,
they're barking up the wrong tree.
I mean, it's like, look.
And then she's like, ah, ah, ah.
And she goes, LOL, I know I'm kind of like for the party.
And then I did like some kind of like weird squiggly thing.
And she's like, yeah.
And then I did like a little penguin,
like that's her like,
that reminded me of her boobs right there.
And then she goes, ha ha ha ha.
And then she goes, so an emoji relationship,
friendship I mean, right, friendship, right?
Was there anything where I'm saying,
you know, anything about,
You know, I'm in love with her. I'm heady on her. Do you see me heady on her anyway sending these emojis?
I don't think this is like leading anybody on or anything. I mean, it's so I mean
It's just like she was friends who I met and I go and I have like a little like a fun fun fun or yeah
And then she goes ho ho ho
And then I go, and then I mean, I'm just being dumb, you know, this is just silly.
And then she's like trying to do these sexy like, you know, Japan and I'm like spicy with spicy hot dog, right?
And then she's like masturbating bear or something.
And then I'm like, yeah.
And then she's like.
And then she gave a heart and I said I have chills being sarcastic, okay?
And she goes ah, so do I don't tell anyone I flirt with you keep it on the down low
And I get I sense a like a heart and then she sends a heart and then I'm dance
I'm just dancing like a cat dancing and then she's like
and then
She sends us something about the Joker and she says you need to post this on YouTube
And then she said, I'm going to remind you to mod me.
And then she posts this kind of stuff about people
that talk about people.
And I said, oh, these are awesome.
I think I unbanned your account.
I will mod you.
Just remind me in the chat.
And I did a little lion.
And then she's like, I'll remind you when you go live.
And I do thumbs up, thumbs up.
OK, this is like, I know this is probably
more conversation than you probably expected,
but I wasn't hitting on her, right?
And she's like, okay, then she got mad at me one night in the chat after I modded her.
She said, you're wrong for that.
I'm going to pour and bomb you, right?
And she's like, just kidding, but stop timing me out.
I won't support you anymore.
And I said, I didn't time you.
I said, I didn't time you once managing mod is, and she goes, whatever.
Something that was censored because it was so perverted. It says let me see it says a message is hidden because it contains sensitive content
It says fuck you and your mods and she's like not my fault. You can't handle mine or JT's opinions
This is like a little hints, right? Sorry about last night
I'm unsubscribing from you and I said all these forgiving and she's like alright making sure well
Make your retard mods leave me alone then by the way be be a married whore like Slayer
And then I made the cat eyes again
then she made she like replied like lapping emojis and then
Then the next thing I know
She got banned her account was banned
Okay, and then so and that from there all it was was like a
This is this isn't me hitting on her like it doesn't he do on her right?
That's me hitting on her so there you go guys I revealed the whole relationship so
Nobody can say anything you saw you saw all the text messages. What do you think guys is that I know it's kind of cringy
Who's that saying this whole one, please be careful what you put in that about others
Hold on
Grim like what I didn't dox anybody her name is not even Vicki
It's like something starts with a C and a B. So why what am I what am I sharing about others?
I'm sharing my my messages, okay
So just so you guys know and yeah, whoever can hide that bully person
Yeah, I guess I'm gonna have to have more of a zero tolerance policy for that kind of nonsense because
Now I have like no stated enemies that right now. There's so the thing is they're so smug about it
They'll just they don't even care. They'll fit the and then they just laugh. Oh cry about it
Okay, I'll cry about it. I'll go cry about it right now to my whole stream. Let them know what piece of the shit
You are okay. How you how you really talk about people especially me who pretend pretend to like and pretend to be nice to you and
You know not taken anymore
What's criminal?
Maybe say Marcy, what's criminal? What did I that I'm criminal if I share my own messages?
Canada dries here. Oh, not me. Okay. Oh, not me. Okay. Well, who's who's hold on?
I'm sorry. I'm missing messages. I'm just
Mean it might have been weird. I mean, I think maybe people get the wrong idea from emojis and stuff
I don't know. What's what's happening here?
Oh, she's watching guys, now she's, and it says hidden.
She just text messes me, so just now.
So she's watching.
Okay, well, you know what, Vicky,
you shouldn't have lied, okay?
You're saying that I'm hitting on you.
I just showed the message is to prove I'm not,
because you're trying to slander me saying I'm like,
you know, being a creep trying to hit on you, okay?
You're being the creep, okay?
Oh my gosh, Marcy, all they do is threaten, you know, it's like,
I mean, it's like in a way probably like, you know, and it's like online. It's like what they're
probably in different state. I mean, it's something I would even like, I'm not concerned about them
actually, like, you know, my physical safety. You know, super guys, if you would have seen her
backstage when she was backstage, she hurt, she was okay, she had like some kind of moomoo on the
There's like these milk bags and she was just like juggling them. It was like almost like juggling them. Okay
Okay, thank you. Oh, thank you. I'm sorry. I miss understand sometimes
Canada oh so thank you. Yeah, he makes me look like a powerlifter. Oh gosh
Psychi, what are you doing?
Doxing is criminal. Marcy's right. Goddy warned you that what happened if you didn't let Tom flash up. Guys, can you please hide that person?
Okay, and uh
No, but placebo. I was just telling the truth. This is what happened to me. That's it
Someone to go backstage and to show that that is like
I feel sexually harassed.
Have you guys, have you seen me like really hit on a guy,
like lately tell a guy to take off a shirt
or a straight guy?
Like I really stopped that because it's like,
I understand like some people might feel uncomfortable
and I don't want people to feel uncomfortable.
But do you imagine what I see backstage?
I mean, I get people, I have some guy
with like the most disgusting feet.
Like show he kept showing his feet backstage or really jerking off
I mean just people are like doing crazy stuff backstage. It's like I don't want to see that
But it's like I'm not gonna like really say, you know, it's not that big of a deal. I can I can handle it
but
I just got I got all now I feel kind of like
Relieved oh gosh. I just I needed it
Guys, I love the truth. I love the truth. I love when the I love when the truth is just revealed
And it's like I don't even have to do it. I like to do a sit-back
Watch be quiet
That was like well there I just thought there was terrible things about someone being said I'd like there's no way
They're talking about me right like I was like they're not and I swole up and it's like oh, you know it's like he's this you know
So my name again being mentioned, right?
Just in Boyle's world. It's like you could go to jail for revenge pouring Vicki showing her books since she turned me down
guys
Yeah
Hold on a second
So how am I so because I told the story that did I like show a video of her?
Did I show a video of her just because I described them?
Hmm acts. I don't know again. I'll look into it acts
I'm not sure if it but by the chat but is like some people have shattered in there
I just I don't know but I'll make you a mod in there because I know you were you're over there
There's that's not many people in there, but I do appreciate I saw you send me some tokens and
Okay, the Tom flash of the clone one, but the thing is like first of all
Like why would somebody clone him, but okay, that's fine
second of all
It was a really bad porn bomb.
It's like the worst kind of porn bomb you can do.
It was kind of like the Dan Schneider kind of
steam porn bomb, if you know my drift,
which is like really bad.
And third of all, I saw that person with the name
and beat his chat that night saying,
oh, I took Psyche down or something
because I ended the stream.
Oh, I have Marcy, oh shoot.
Okay, but yeah, I might respond to something because I didn't understand one of your comments, but yeah, it wasn't
You subscribe for a month on Twitch. Oh cool. It's two dollars
Okay, and by the way, if you have Amazon Prime
You can get a free membership too
And if you have Amazon Prime and you go follow my Twitch or go up you can actually like
Pick one person like one creator on Twitch and if it's me, I'll be honored
But you can find somebody if you have somebody else, you know, whoever you want to give it to you
I mean, I won't but you know, I'm just psyche awakens on Twitch
But if you have a twitch membership through the Amazon, right?
First of all, which is pretty cool because you can get free video games and stuff
But if you have the Amazon thing you can subscribe
To me like basically you get one free membership. So you get one creator. You get a free membership for a month
And so if you were to do that on me, I'd probably get a couple bucks
I'm not sure how much but
So, you know, that'd be cool
If it doesn't cost anybody anything and it's a way to support if you just want to support
Like that, you know, because that's pretty much free or support wherever you want to because it's pretty cool that I think
No, you get to do that through Amazon
But I'll look into the, I'll look into that, the chatting thing for you, Axe, okay?
Through the Amazon thing, yeah. Well, because I guess Twitch is, I guess Amazon owns or something like that because they integrated it and so
Yeah, you can just go if you go through to Amazon and then go to Twitch through Amazon because you get a free subscription as a prime member
It will tell you kind of like oh you can support one creator a month. So
Pretty cool
No, no, he won't if he becomes a member, I'll just hide him, you know, it's like I don't mind hiding like
There's but he's not gonna ever become a member that would require him paying $5. I don't I don't see that he would ever
You know, it's like that would that would give you know help me with like, you know
I'd probably make you know two dollars and you couldn't have that right? They're just haters guys these people are haters
They're on a discord, you know plotting on taking people down. They think it's a game
They look for people that they think are like, you know
You know little cows or
Accenture or anything. I mean they're bullies. They're bullies, right?
Pure bullies
Troll, Troll-ish. I don't see anything redeeming.
I don't know that Jaws Brever might be one of them, right?
If you subscribe, you get a wrench. No, you do not. You do not get a wrench if you subscribe.
You uh, I have enough moderators. There are channels that do that you can go to the good pussy channel
And she'll give you a wrench if you become a member. Okay, or subscribe. I do not do that
I mean, I I will just have to be
wrenching people I trust won't and uh
Let me see wait if you excel it says Marx is your bodyguard
Tall bold man California tall bald man in California. Okay. Okay, let's see if I subscribe for $3. Well, my channel is $5. So that's not possible
Or are you talking about on switch? What are you talking about?
And don't talk about beta, please you're about to get banned
Because first of all, Bita's my friend, and I don't talk about her negatively, okay?
Oh, also, what else do I have? On TikTok, I'm already, I have a membership there.
I think it's, I changed it to like $2.99, plus like there's a two-week free trial. So, I don't know.
We're just trying different things and stuff like that.
Yeah, yeah, hold on and I will I'll make sure Marcy mod it. I'm not sure what happened there. Hold on
Yeah, so Marcy, you know, you know what to do Marcy if you see if you see these people
Just please help me out and
We're gonna we're gonna clean this up. We got this, okay
Yeah, just they're left not like people I'm also allowed not to have to have them in my chat every night rooting my show taking down the vibe
scaring people away harassing my guests harassing me calling me terrible
And you're let it go not like me from your discord where I don't have to see it. Don't do it right in public
I mean, it's like well, it's really no now. I've seen it right. They did it right in front of me, but
You know, go go do it in private and you just hate me have a little hate group and just be silent in the chat
Why do I have to put up with you? I don't have to put up with them, right?
Are you three dollars to switch? Oh, thank you. That's awesome placebo
I think which is a pretty good. Oh pretty good website, too
You know, but if you do have Amazon Prime, I think you can cash in a free membership through them, too
So any even if you've already remember, I think you can still cash in on like, you know
Getting another subscription or something like that
Yeah, it's what it says all they'll try to get you in discord. Am I scared?
You know what?
I'm not afraid of them
They revealed to me like just how how sad small empathetic they really are, right? They're not powerful. They're not
They they you know what they think they're hot shit, but they're just cold diarrhea. Okay
Placebo go to hell who's this person placebo go to hell don't talk about beta. I told you just not to talk about beta and here you go
Bye
Do you like that line?
That's pretty good.
Actually, I stole that line from one of my favorite movies,
it's called Welcome to the Dollhouse.
I don't think I've ever saw the movie Welcome to the Dollhouse.
Yeah, you don't think CFF?
What does CFF stand for?
I've never heard of that.
CFF, does anybody know?
Is that a show?
They just want to take over my panel. Well, no, they can't
They're not going to my panel. That's why my panel is very my panel is very exclusive
Guys, I got poor mom so many times. I have to be more careful about just like bringing people up
I'm not gonna let a new people. I'm really they need to really prove people needs to prove
I need to know people from now on if I bring my panel and it's like so if they want to come on panel and get a reading or something
You know
I need to I need to have a conversation with them first in the chat, right?
Yeah
Yeah, Marcy chat. Oh, okay CFF. Oh chat friends forever. Okay, so you said
Their name is that their name is like a gang name chat friends forever JT
Goddy rain Vicki Empress Chinchilla
Lula, Zico, Queen T, and Billy Hayden.
Guys, you see those names?
I like this person right here.
This person seems like they know some information.
Instead of the information,
I'm just gonna give them a chance, okay?
Can you, and if you see those people,
can you please ban all those people?
I don't want the chat friends forever.
I don't wanna be their friend forever.
Chat friends never again, okay?
Hey Nick, what's it was? Oh my god. What is the topic? The topic is how we're gonna be banning people like you Nick, okay?
People like even if someone has a name like that. No
The topic is how you're not gonna be part of the chat. Oh
Dubs, oh Wubs. Yes, or Dub Dub was he was really really really cool. Yeah
I was, you know, having a bad night of course, and then he came up and I was like, who is this person?
I was like, I didn't know who he was. And he had come up before, you know,
I think he was maybe skeptical of terror or something with or something, you know,
and I had maybe to take him off the panel one time, but he came and he had a good talk with me and
you know, it was a good chat and it was like, you know, very much calm me down and
Because it's like they were saying I'm some paranoid tweaker or whatever, but there and here they are
They're doing exactly what I thought so that's not called paranoia. That's called. I was I was right
I just had to need to trust my intuition, right?
Yeah, I'm not well, I'm not emotionally invested. He's live. Well, and there's Vicki. Okay. Well
Everyone
Go go run to go run to JT, you know JT guys don't I would I would just avoid that person
He's gonna like try to dox you he's gonna he doxes
You know, you know, physically handicapped minors, okay?
That's that's what he does. Okay. Why did I even have my chat? I don't know. I'm like retarded
Okay, yeah, that was that was good and like easy and I also like we swear things away easy at least honest with me
I think you know, but it's like maybe if I do get paranoid it's because of them
Right and it's like they made me paranoid because of their behavior
And then they try to misdirect it to like other people so it's like I think it's other people and so it's confusing sometimes
So that I need to get he's threatening me on his show
Okay, can guys can somebody like get a video of that just so I have that of
Somebody making threats on public
If somebody can get a clip that for me, I'd appreciate that.
Okay?
Because I think making threats is illegal.
Right?
Not only physical threats or threats of doxing, I just want, I need the evidence.
Okay?
I already have the, and Spunky, you know, I think she'll, she'll keep that evidence of
what happened on her show, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna step it guys. There's absolutely no gonna be no doxing at all if people bring up anybody's last name if they bring up any
any other information, I mean it's like
It's it's depending on if you know it's public
You know some some people are more public than others
But if it's like I don't the problem is I don't know some of the people they put the photos up of and so the people think I'm
Being complacent about it. I have no idea what's going on sometimes, right?
And I finish this burger a big max around here somewhere. Where's my big Mac?
Look at the fridge. Oh, no, I did
And McDonald's again
Lola has a she's my little RBF my little RBF
He always looks kind of pissed off, huh? He looks so mad my little babe
This is tricks his mom
Lola Lola
You get her cute freckles on her belly
What are you doing?
It's up here on your couch. I'll comfy on the blanket
Hmm
The north outside, I think I think Lola is the only one in here right now one of the apartment tour I can finally give you one
Listen clean okay, it's staircase my living room
Okay
There's the
They have a cat some cat trees and stuff
My bedroom is oh here's um, there's Rudy right here here. This isn't one of my desk
Rudy having some food
Show you my bedroom
This is some stuff on the bed, but yeah
It's like it's all it's all I need to pull this laundry, but yeah, you can see hi guys
Some art
That room so working on that a little bit kitchen
Okay, you see it's not like I mean I still have to do a little bit of more intensive cleaning, but you know I've done a lot of
I'm second exposed live at JTS.
Okay, guys, what's the, let's see,
let's go do a raid on his channel.
Let's go raid his channel.
Can someone post his channel here?
Guys, can someone post his channel?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you live stream. You're you're a real one
Guys
Let me go over there right now. I don't know if you guys know the channel name. What's it called? Hold on. Let's see
Fuck you have to pay 15 million well good luck
I would buy a hundred dollars to my name. I
Won't give you ten cents. Okay, JT
Supposed, okay, there you go guys. Thank you. Let's go over there. Okay. I'll see you over there
But I'm not gonna be saying anything. Okay. Bye